<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<Item>
		<Name>CallWebservice</Name>
    <DisplayName>Call Web Service</DisplayName>
    <Description>A Web Service is a method of communication between two electronic devices over http. You can use a Web Service to pull in some information generated by another application onto a Stadium page</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>Decision</Name>
		<DisplayName>Decision (If/Else)</DisplayName>
		<Description>Decisions allow for the definition of conditional statements. On the page, these statements will execute some functionality according to a specific condition.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>ExecuteSQL</Name>
    <DisplayName>Execute SQL</DisplayName>
    <Description>ExecuteSQL allows the application to connect to MSSQL or Oracle databases and execute a SQL statement. When using MSSQL you can also run stored procedures.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>ForEach</Name>
    <DisplayName>For Each</DisplayName>
    <Description>Loop through a comma separated list of values and for each value do a certain action.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>GetFile</Name>
    <DisplayName>Get File</DisplayName>
    <Description>The component will fetch a file from the server and request the user to download it.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>MessageBox</Name>
    <DisplayName>Message Box</DisplayName>
    <Description>The component uses a JQuery dialog window to display some information or request a decision from a user. </Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>NavigateToPage</Name>
    <DisplayName>Navigate To Page</DisplayName>
    <Description>You can use this component to navigate the user away from a page and onto another one.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>Notification</Name>
		<DisplayName>Notification</DisplayName>
		<Description>You can use this component to display a notification to the user.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>SetOutputParameter</Name>
    <DisplayName>Set Output Parameter</DisplayName>
    <Description>Output parameters are placeholders for values the script will return when finished. Use SetOutputParameter to define the value of a script output parameter.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>SetValue</Name>
		<DisplayName>Set Value</DisplayName>
		<Description>SetValue is used for setting the values of the various script elements.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>SetVariable</Name>
    <DisplayName>Set Variable</DisplayName>
    <Description>Variables are placeholders for values inside a script. Use SetVariable to define the value of a script variable.</Description>
	</Item>
	<Item>
		<Name>Variable</Name>
    <DisplayName>Variable</DisplayName>
    <Description>Variables are placeholders for values inside a script. They can be initialised with a value or set using the SetValue action.</Description>
	</Item>
</ArrayOfItem>
